https://kumaran.com/privacy-policy/

Industries
Every organization is different; every industry is even more so. At Kumaran, we have carefully honed varied industry expertise so that we understand your business in-depth. Beyond gathering just IT expertise, our teams strive to know your industry a little better, observe current trends, and comprehend how it works so that we can tailor solutions to your unique concerns and opportunities.
Banking
Telecom
Education
Shipping
Insurance
Retail
services
Migration Services
Products
Every organization is different; every industry is even more so. At Kumaran, we have carefully honed varied industry expertise so that we understand your business in-depth. Beyond gathering just IT expertise, our teams strive to know your industry a little better, observe current trends, and comprehend how it works so that we can tailor solutions to your unique concerns and opportunities.
overview
MAINFRAME APP CONVERTER - NxTran
Forms*Converter
GUI Converter
Object Converter
Program Scanner
Mobile Converter
BLOGSBlogs
About us
Every organization is different; every industry is even more so. At Kumaran, we have carefully honed varied industry expertise so that we understand your business in-depth. Beyond gathering just IT expertise, our teams strive to know your industry a little better, observe current trends, and comprehend how it works so that we can tailor solutions to your unique concerns and opportunities.
overview
leadership
alliances
quality
vision
news & events
join us
Every organization is different; every industry is even more so. At Kumaran, we have carefully honed varied industry expertise so that we understand your business in-depth. Beyond gathering just IT expertise, our teams strive to know your industry a little better, observe current trends, and comprehend how it works so that we can tailor solutions to your unique concerns and opportunities.
why kumaran
life @ kumaran
learning Engagement & development
current openings
apply
Privacy Policy
Effective Date: December 28, 2018
Overview
We at Kumaran Systems respect the privacy of our visitors and are committed to preserving your online safety by preserving your privacy at anytime you visit or communicate/interact with our site. Any visitor entering into our site is deemed to have accepted to the information in this privacy policy.
Our Terms of Use and Privacy Policy offers you a thorough explanation regarding your personal data provided to any data or us we may collect from you.
Information Collection
Data can be collected and processed during the operations of our website. The following are ways we may perform these actions:
Data regarding your visit(s) to our website and any resources used are collected. The following is included and not limited to: location data, web logs, traffic data, and any other communication information.
Any forms you filled out on our site allow us to collect data such as registration form information. We will, where necessary, obtain your explicit consent to collect and use such information.
If for any reason you communicate with our personnel or site we may collect information.
Cookies Usage
There are instances where we may use cookies to gather information regarding our services in a mathematical collection for our website and our advertisers.
Any information collected will not have any identifying data. It is statistical data about our visitors and how they have used our site. No personal details will be shared that could identify you unless you permit us to do so or required by any law in force.
We may assemble information about your common internet use with a cookie file. When used, the cookies are downloaded to your computer automatically. The cookie is stored on the hard drive, with transferred information. The data sought by the cookie helps us improve our website and any service offered to you.
Your browser has the ability to decline cookies. This is done by setting your browser options to decline all cookies. Note: If you decline the download of cookies, some aspects of our site may not work or allow you access.
Manage Cookies
Please note that you can block cookies by activating the setting on your browser that allows you to refuse the setting of all or some cookies. However, if you use your browser settings to block all cookies (including essential cookies) you may not be able to access all or part of our site.
For your convenience we’ve provided links to the cookie management page for the most popular web browsers:
Chrome
Internet Explorer
Firefox
Safari
Opera
Use of Information
Information stored or collected regarding you, helps us improve and offer services you need. The following list contains how we might use your data:
Any request you make of our site or personnel allows us to use information you provided us with, relating to the products or services we have. We may also send information on products or services you may be interested in, as long as consent has been received.
Contract Commitments: To meet any Commitment we make to you.
Changes or Improvements made to the site can warrant use of your information, with regard to notification of such changes.
We may use data or allow third parties to use information that is not related to goods or services you may be interested in. We or third parties contact you only if consent has been provided by you at anytime, based on information we collected.
Any new customer can only be contacted by us or third parties if consent has been offered via our site. We only send communications you have consented to.
Anyone who does not wish to give consent for our site or third party use has the opportunity to decline. Once we receive your withhold for consent we will remove your details from any mailings or third party communications. In case we do not receive any response from you to limit the access of your information, it shall be deemed that you consent to such distribution of your information as mentioned above.
None of the information collected about you will offer identifiable characteristics. Information shared to a third party is statistical only. We will not reveal who you are, but generate mathematical / statistical information about our visitors.
Personal Data Storage and Security
We maintain security measures designed to provide reasonable protection for your personal data against loss, misuse, unauthorized access, disclosure, and alteration. The security measures include firewalls, data encryption, physical access controls to our data centers, and information access authorization controls. You are responsible for verifying that the personal data we maintain about you is accurate and current. We also take all reasonable action to ensure the safety of your personal data in agreement with this Privacy Policy.
Information we are provided will be stored on secure servers. You should understand data via online transmission is not completely secure. We cannot guarantee full protection and security data, only that we take all reasonable action to protect information sent to us electronically. Transmission of any data by you is at your own risk.
We collect and store the data as provided by you and we shall not vouch the correctness of the data provided by you.
Personal Data Retention
We retain personal data to fulfill our legal or regulatory obligations and for our business purposes. We may retain personal data for longer periods than required by law if it is in our legitimate business interests and not prohibited by laws.
We will continue to use and disclose such personal data in accordance with this privacy policy.
Information Disclosure
At times, we may disclose personal information to persons in our group. This can include subsidiaries, holding companies, or any other subsidiaries involved in our business, if applicable. Third Party disclosure may occur for the following reasons:
Selling any or all of our business to a third party may result in sharing your information.
At any time when we are legally required to we may disclose information about you and your visits to our sites without your consent in cases of the prosecution and punishment for offenses.
To prevent fraud and help in fraud protection in order to reduce credit risk, we may disclose information.
Personal information may also be disclosed to law enforcement, regulatory, or other government agencies, or to other third parties, in each case to comply with legal or regulatory obligations or request.
Third Party Links
Third party links may be discovered on our site. These third party links have their own privacy policy, which you agree to when you click on the link. We are not responsible nor do we accept responsibility for third party links. Our liability covers us only on our site, and thus we do not accept liability for third party links, as we have no control over them.
Information Accessibility
We cannot withhold data we collect about you, as per The Data Protection Act 1998. This act provides you with access to any information we may hold on you. If you wish to have access about our data collection on you please use the contact details below to formulate your data access request.
Grievance Addressing
Any grievance or complaint, in relation to processing of information, should be addressed in writing to Kumaran’s designated Grievance Officer, who shall address the grievances as expeditiously as possible, preferably within 30 days from the date of receipt.
E-mail:  grievance-officer@kumaran.com
Contact Us
Please feel free to contact us with queries, requests, or comments you may have about our Privacy Policy. We welcome any communication via the email address supplied here: grievance-officer@kumaran.com This Privacy Policy is updated from time to time; therefore, it should be reviewed occasionally.
Copyright 2019 kumaran systems.All rights reserved
privacy policy | Site Map
